Finding Aid for Paul Winston McCracken papers, 1940-2011
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Visual Materials
  - Videocassettes
    - Carl S. Minden, Director of Corporate Relations, University of Utah (Box 26)
    - Tribute to President Dwight D. Eisenhower, January 29, 1986 (Box 26)
- Sound Recordings
  - "Can the U.S. Regain its Capability for Orderly Expansion", 4 audiocassettes (Box 26)
  - Hillsdale College Center for Constructive Alternatives Conference, 9 audiocassettes in case (Box 26)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 26)